

DANIFI BABILONIA

Frontend Web Developer and Bilingual Customer Service Representative

About Me

I'm a developer with experience in building websites for small and medium sized businesses. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store - I can help.

I also worked for eBay as Bilingual Customer Service Representative for more than a year, so I can provide a really good insight when it comes from e-commerce platforms or ÚX-UI desings!

Experience

2023 - Act. **Technical Support Specialist**

Kodland

As a part-time Technical Support Specialist, I diagnosed and resolved software and hardware issues, configured systems, documented customer inquiries, and provided timely feedback. My problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to work independently and as part of a team contributed to my success in this role.

2022 - Act. Frontend Desings

Creating projects and layout of web pages by using Bootstrap, Bootswatch and Redux

Creation of Various Projects and Activities 2022 - Act Academio

API implementation activities and responsive webpage layout using React.

Bilingual Customer Service Representative 2021 - 2023 Teleperformance

For over a year, I worked as a Bilingual Customer Service Representative in the Payments LÓB of eBay, where I acquired customer service skills in a bilingual environment and was able to develop my problem-solving and teamwork abilities.

Contact Me

(+57) 301 405 6354 Medellin - Antioquia (Open to dantealigheri.1998@gmail.com **Additional Information:** Portfolio Web

Education

Computer Systems and Engineering

Full Stack Web Developer

Lenguages

English







Spanish





Skills and Lenguages



React IS













HTML **PSQL**



DANIEL BABILONIA

Desarrollador Web Frontend y Representante de Servicio al cliente Bilingüe

Sobre Mi

Soy un desarrollador con experiencia en la creación de sitios web para pequeñas y medianas empresas. Ya sea que esté tratando de ganar trabajo, listar sus servicios o incluso crear una tienda en línea completa, puedo ayudar.

Además, trabajé como Representante de servicio al cliente bilingüe para eBay durante más de un año, por lo que puedo proporcionar una excelente perspectiva en cuanto a plataformas de comercio electrónico o diseños de UX-UI".

Experiencia

2023 - Act. Technical Support Specialist

Codland

Como Especialista en Soporte Técnico, diagnosticaba y resolvía problemas de software y hardware, configuraba sistemas, documentaba consultas de clientes y proporcionaba comentarios oportunos. Mis habilidades para resolver problemas, atención al detalle y capacidad para trabajar de manera independiente y en equipo contribuyeron a mi éxito en este rol.

2022 - Act. Desarrollo Frontend

Freelance

Creacion de proyectos y maquetacion de paginas web utilizando herramientas como Bootstrap, Boostwatch

2022 - Act Creación de Proyectos y Actividades

andomi

Actividades de implementacion de API's y maquetación de paginas web responsivas en React

2021 - 2023 Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe.

Teleperformance

Durante más de un año trabajé como Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe en el LOB de Payments de eBay, donde adquirí habilidades en atención al cliente en un ambiente bilingüe y pude desarrollar mi capacidad de solución de problemas y trabajo en equipo.

Contacto

(+57) 301 405 6354 Sincelejo - Sucre (Abierto a cambios) dantealigheri.1998@gmail.com

<u>Additional Information:</u>
<u>Portfolio Web</u> (Click Aquí)

Educación

Ingenieria de Sistemas y Computacion

Universidad del Norte 2016 - 2019

Desarollador Web FullStack

Escuela de Ciencias de Computacion Academlo 2022 - Presente

Idiomas

Inglés





Habilidades



React IS



CSS



HTML



PSQL